dmasoftlab.com 2018-12-31

# Radius, Mikrotik, Cisco, ChilliSpot, StarOS, pfSense, DD-WRT, DOCSIS (WLAN, PPPoE, VPN, Hotspot, Dialup) ISP billing

Privacy Notice

Our Commitment To Privacy

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested. 

The Information We Collect

This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the **dmasoftlab.com** website. On some pages, you can order products, make requests, and register to receive materials. The types of personal information collected at these pages are: 

  * Name 
  * Address 
  * Email address 
  * Phone number 
  * etc.

The Way We Use Information

We use the **information** you provide about yourself when placing an order only to **complete that order**. We **do not share** this information with **outside parties** except to the extent necessary to complete that order. 

We use the information you provide about someone else when placing an order only to ship the product and to confirm delivery. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order. 

We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive. Such addresses are not shared with outside parties. 

Your **email address** can be used to **receive updates** on our new products and services. These email **notifications can be disabled** in our portal.

You can **request deletion** of your **personal data** any time.

You have the right to **access your information** via a subject access request which will be provided within a month. If any data is inaccurate, we'll correct it. 

We never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses. 

Cookies

The website www.dmasoftlab.com doesn't use tracking cookies.

Our Commitment To Data Security

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. 

How To Contact Us 

Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please send us an email at **info[at]dmasoftlab.com**
